<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Ottsonic]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Ottsonic]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/ottsonic/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2016 13:52:52 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/ottsonic/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Any mix engineer worth her salt will be working to make every song translate to every kind of reproduction environment, from iPhone speakers to a big club rig. That said, the practice of supplying different mixes for different end uses is long established - remember the 12" 'Club Mix' from the 1980s, which was usually stripped out and extended and mixed with more bass drum and quieter vocals.  You don't see "Radio Mix' and 'Club Mix' so much these days because the reproduction characteristics of both environments has moved closer together. Nobody listens to AM radio anymore and internet/DAB radio has a much wider frequency response than radio of twenty years ago. A mix which works on the DAB radio in your kitchen will probably scale up to a 50kw Funktion One rig quite nicely.  As well, FM radio output processing is a lot more transparent these days [the digital Optimod was introduced during the 1990s] and you don't hear the kind of overt radio compression that was in vogue during the 1970s and 1980s. I remember switching between Capital Radio and Radio One on my bedside clock/radio in about 1980 and preferring Capital because it sounded louder and more exciting. I read a few years back that there was a whole culture of competition between those two stations based upon how they set their Optimod and the pitch at which they played back records. Capital played everything at +10% pitch and with a much hotter output and the bottom end cranked up so it sounded more energetic and it certainly worked on me; enough to make me put up with adverts for sheepskin jackets and jean shops every seven minutes.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ottsonic/any-mix-engineer-worth-her-salt-will-be-working-to-make-ever/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4f238008-b26f-4b7c-8a7b-32f049a34171</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2016 13:52:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>A cheap hardware reverb is unlikely to sound better [or even as good] as a good plugin reverb. All digital reverbs, whether plugins or outboard, use the same types of algorithm to generate their effect, whilst the hardware version will also need to include a case, power supply, display, physical memory, input and output converters, etc, in the price.  A £300 hardware reverb won't sound any better than a £50 plugin and a £130 plugin reverb will kick the arse off any hardware reverb you can get for </p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ottsonic/a-cheap-hardware-reverb-is-unlikely-to-sound-better-or-even/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">48a62ed6-10f1-4f10-97a9-bb6c3eb433c9</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Make Noise Erbe-Verb]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Make Noise Erbe-Verb</h1><p>The Erbe-Verb is more than a collection of reverb algorithms or presets, it is a unique, modeless, continuously variable reverb algorithm with complete voltage control. Typical reverb types such as plate, room, hall, shimmer and others may be programmed by adjusting the knobs. The continuously variable algorithm allows for hybrid and unreal spaces to be found.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/fc4a80ba4854bdc3a420c12b9ab8162f01afe774.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ik8CIQ8Dd8E</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a79b24fb-4f05-4232-983a-b57bf046dd3b</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 21:32:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>